Guide to the ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1953-1991
  - Anastasio, John, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Letter to Chaikin re sweatshop conditions in NYC.
  - Annual Civil Rights Institute, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Anonymous Letters, 1975-1984 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Letters from individuals with complaints about wages, working conditions, union leadership and other grievances.
  - Apparel Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Applications for Union Positions, 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Arbeit, Nathalie, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Argentina, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    Reports of trip to Argentina and meeting with labor leaders.
  - Arnold and Porter Consulting Group, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Includes a feasibility study of 5 ILGWU properties.
  - Aron, Bruno, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Artisans Cooperative, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Correspondence and related documents re homework.
  - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Association for a Better New York, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Association for Children With Learning Disabilities, 1975-1983 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    re fund raising activities.
  - Association of Scientific Technical and Managerial Staffs, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Association for Social Economics, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Astrow, Irving, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association, Inc [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1986 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    Correspondence re contract demands, unfair labor practices, proposals for negotiations, imports, depressed state of the domestic garment industry.
  - Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association, Inc [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1986 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Atlantic Benefit Fund, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States [folder 1 of 3], 1975-1987 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    (Chaikin, member, Board of Directors) Includes papers and reports of various working groups on subjects such as military service, Greece and Turkey, trade reform, NATO, arms control and others.
  - Atlantic Council of the United States [folder 2 of 3], 1975-1987 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States [folder 3 of 3], 1975-1987 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Atlantic Richfield Company, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    Correspondence with Robert Anderson, Chairman of the Board, re Economic Policy Council plans and activities.
  - Australia, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    Correspondence and report concerning labor movement in Australia.
  - Autographs, 1977-1986 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    Includes requests for Chaikin's autograph.
  - Awards [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    Includes correspondence re Chaikin awards from Jewish Labor Committee, Histadrut, Eugene V. Debs Award, Covenant of Peace Award, and others.
  - Awards [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1981 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - B and B Manufacturing Company, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Baker, Ralph, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Letter from an anti-union person from Vermont.
  - Ballon, Charles, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Banks, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Basic Books, Inc., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Bear Stearns Asset Management, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Beit Hagefen [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    (Arab-Jewish Cultural Community and Youth Centre) Related routine.
  - Beit Hagefen [folder 2 of 2], 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Bendix, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bergen Community College, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Report and correspondence re conference on the Future of Higher Education in a Technological Society.
  - Berley and Company, Inc., 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Biderman Industries USA, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bingaman (Jeff). Breakfast, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Correspondence re fund raising and support of Bingaman (Senator from New Mexico).
  - Black Americans to Support Israel Committee, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc., 1986 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Bolmer, John E., 1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Boston Company, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Bowen, Robert, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Bowen, Sarah, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Brandeis University [folder 1 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Trustees) Includes minutes, reports, brochures and correspondence re activities, meeting arrangements and establishment of the Sol C. Chaikin Chair in National Health Policy at the Heller Graduate School, Brandeis University.
  - Brandeis University [folder 2 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Brandeis University [folder 3 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Brandeis University [folder 4 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Brandeis University [folder 5 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Brandeis University [folder 6 of 6], 1976-1991 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Brandeis University/Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center. Benefit Dinner [folder 1 of 4], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    Correspondence and guest lists re fund raising drive and testimonial dinner in Chaikin's honor.
  - Brandeis University/Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center. Benefit Dinner [folder 2 of 4], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Brandeis University/Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center. Benefit Dinner [folder 3 of 4], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Brandeis University/Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center. Benefit Dinner [folder 4 of 4], 1983 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Brazil [folder 1 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Includes correspondence, papers and articles re trip to Brazil (1977) as member of Commission on United States-Brazilian Relations.
  - Brazil [folder 2 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Brazil [folder 3 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Brazil [folder 4 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Brazil [folder 5 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Brazil [folder 6 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Brazil [folder 7 of 7], 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - British American Tours, Inc., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - British Embassy, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - British Trades Union Congress, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Chaikin sent as Fraternal Delegate representing the AFL-CIO at the 113th Trades Union Congress in London.
  - Brock, William E., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Secretary of Labor, Brock, to Chaikin on his accomplishments and wishing him a well earned retirement.
  - Brookings Institution, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    re Chaikin's participation on Roundtable on National Issues as a 1977 member.
  - Brownsville Manufacturing Company, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Correspondence re issues covered in contract negotiations with ILGWU and arbitration fees.
  - Bureau of National Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Burlington Industries, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    With William Klopman, Chairman of the Board re imports of apparel.
  - Business/Labor Working Group [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Correspondence concerning improvement of NYC's economy and to strengthen its job base; 39 p. confidential draft, "Summary Report of the B/LWG on Jobs and Economic Regeneration in NYC"; meeting notes; minutes.
  - Business/Labor Working Group [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Buthelezi, M. Gatsha, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Correspondence and lists of persons attending luncheon in honor of Chief Buthelezi, Chief Minister of Kwazulu, South Africa.
  - Butler, Landon, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Includes article in Newsweek re PATCO strike by Landon.
  - Buy U.S.A., 1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Cabot, Stephen, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Cambodia Crisis Committee (AFL-CIO), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    re nationwide relief program to assist the Cambodians.
  - Campaign, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    re Garment Center political rally financing.
  - Carey, Hugh L., 1975-1982 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Correspondence re Garment Industry Job Retention Act; aid to community colleges; economic policy; Committee for the FDR Centennial; Chaikin served as member of NYS Governor's Council on International Business; 19 p. paper by Chaikin, "Employment in the Textile and Clothing Industries"; increasing exports; political contributions; and related routine.
  - Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    re increased apparel imports.
  - Carnegie Endowment For International Peace, 1978-1982 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    91 p. report, "Trade Policy Panel Report" by Economic Policy Council-UNA-USA, 1979; correspondence re world trade relations.
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Correspondence re Middle East Peace Settlement; public endorsement of Carter's re-election; personal notes and invitations; inflation; national health program; and other issues.
  - Carter, Jimmy. White House Staff, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    Re Equal Rights Amendment; letters thanking Chaikin for his assistance in various efforts.
  - Carter, Rosalynn, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Re her acceptance of the Parsons School of Design Award; Thanking the Chaikins for attending White House dinner in honor of the Prime Minister of Japan & related routine.
  - Center For Corporate Public Involvement, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Center For Democracy, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Center For Inter-American Relations, 1977-1982 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    Member; correspondence re speech by Chaikin on U.S.-Chile relations and related routine.
  - Center For Migration Studies, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Center For National Policy [folder 1 of 3], 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    Member; presentation of Distinguished Public Service Award to Chaikin; trade policy project; financial support and related routine.
  - Center For National Policy [folder 2 of 3], 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Center For National Policy [folder 3 of 3], 1981-1987 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Center For Strategic and International Studies, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Includes papers presented at CSIS Quadrangular Forum and related routine.
  - Center For the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Cerbone, Richard, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    Re charge of age discrimination against the ILGWU.
  - Chaikin, Eric B. (son), 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    Includes a request through Eric Chaikin, Attorney, from the Pennsylvania Crime Commission to arrange an interview with Sol Chaikin re organized crime infiltration of the garment industry; and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Rosalind, 1974-1985 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    Personal note from Mrs. Jimmy Carter; letter from Jimmy Carter thanking Chaikin for attending funeral of Golda Meir (includes Mrs. Chaikin's handwritten notes); correspondence re working with children with learning disabilities; abortion issue; and other related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Articles, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 34a)
    Includes articles by Chaikin. (see also Box 52)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Awards (Box 20, Folder 35)
    Declined B'nai B'rith Gold Medallion Award; includes requests for autographs and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Biographies [folder 1 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 36)
    Includes requests for and copies of biographies.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Biographies [folder 2 of 2] (Box 20, Folder 36a)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Cards (Box 20, Folder 37)
    Holiday greeting cards.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 1 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Includes hundreds of notes and letters of congratulations upon his election as Secretary-Treasurer of ILGWU and later his election to the presidency from individuals and organizations around the world.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 2 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 3 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 4 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 5 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 6 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Congratulations [folder 7 of 7], 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Dinners [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, programs, etc. re dinners honoring Chaikin. Social Democrats, USA; Histadrut Humanitarian Award; Towsend Harris Medal (Alumni Assn. of the City College of N.Y.); Four Freedoms Award from the Italian-American Labor Council; Labor Human Rights Award from Jewish Labor Committee; and Consumer Merit Award.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Dinners [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1986 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Greetings (from Chaikin) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Includes personal and business letters from Chaikin to various individuals for many types of occasions.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Hoffman, Kim (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Re gift of painting to Chaikin.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Histadrut [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Correspondence re Egyptian and Israeli labour movements; building projects in Israel and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Histadrut [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1983 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. ILGWU Holiday Cards (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Installation of Chair in National Health Policy, Brandeis University, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Documents re chair established in honor of Chaikin.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. New Year [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Greeting cards.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. New Year [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Organizations and Committees [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Correspondence with Save the Children, Foundation For the Restoration and Preservation of Ellis Island, Yivo Institute for Jewish Research, Committee for Economic Development, National Consumers League, Center for Migration Studies, Congresswomen's Caucus Corporation, League of Women Voters, and others.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Organizations and Committees [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    Correspondence re invitations for speaking engagements at conferences, dinners and related routine personal.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Correspondence from individuals requesting Chaikin's assistance in obtaining jobs, and related routine personal.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    Includes letters of sympathy re the death of Chaikin's father; personal with Lawrence F. O'Brien, Special Assistant to the President; and related routine personal.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    Correspondence re assistance in obtaining visas for immigrants for friends and other related routine personal.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    Congratulation letters upon his appointment as General Secretary-Treasurer and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    Letters of thanks for speeches, etc.; note from Edward Kennedy, and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    Includes documents re his travel as a worker-advisor to the ILO Conference in Geneva, and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Includes letter from David Hartman of "Good Morning America" thanking Chaikin for his appearance and other related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Correspondence re honorary degree from Rutgers University and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Correspondence re article in Nation, "The Great Japan Debate"; political contributions and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    4 p. speech by Gov. Mario Cuomo at Tribute honoring Chaikin; and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 1 of 3], 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Correspondence re 1984 Massachusetts AFL-CIO Gompers/Murray/Meany Award to Chaikin; Chaikin's appearance on the "Today" show discussing the issue of U.S./China trade; letters of congratulations on Chaikin's appointment as Chairman of the Convention Center Operating Corporation; selected delegate to the 1984 Democratic National Convention; political contributions and other related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 2 of 3], 1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 3 of 3], 1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Sympathy letters re death of Vice-President Edward Schneider; re political contributions; letters from Geraldine Ferraro, Edward Koch, Ted Kennedy, Elizabeth Holtzman, Edmund Muskie, Richard Gephardt, Mario Cuomo, David Rockefeller and others.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Personal, 1986-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Letters re Chaikin's retirement/dinner and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Politicians and Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 3], 1959-1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Correspondence with Ted Kennedy, Daniel Moynihan, Jimmy Carter, Ed Koch, Mrs. George McGovern, Milton Shapp and miscellaneous and related routine.
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Politicians and Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 3], 1959-1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Chaikin, Sol C. Politicians and Miscellaneous [folder 3 of 3], 1959-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Chile [folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Reports and related documents re Chaikin's AFL-CIO solidarity visit to Chile.
  - Chile [folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Chile [folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - China, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Correspondence re American labor leaders visit to China.
  - Chinatown, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    "The Chinatown Garment Industry Study," 259 p.
  - Citizens' Committee for Immigration Reform, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    (Chaikin, member) Correspondence re concerns with U.S. immigration policy.
  - Citizen's Commission on Indochinese Refugees, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 16a)
  - Citizens for Safe Nuclear Energy, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Correspondence requesting Chaikin to join as a charter member.
  - Citizens for the Constitution, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    Correspondence re group against calling for a new constitutional convention for purposes of an amendment requiring a balanced budget.
  - City College, CUNY, 1978-1984 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    re honorary degree and related routine.
  - City of Hope, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    re financial contributions.
  - City Venture Corporation, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Claiborne, Liz, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    re imports.
  - Clyde Sportswear, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    re Health and Welfare Fund indebtedness.
  - Coalition For A Democratic Majority, 1974-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    (Chaikin, member Board of Directors) Includes 34 p. draft 1984 platform on foreign policy and national defense; minutes; by-laws; and miscellaneous correspondence.
  - Coalition to Save New York (formally Coalition For New York), 1974-1981 (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
    (Chaikin, Executive Committee Member) Correspondence re meetings, activities, legislative action of the Coalition.
  - Coalition for Asian Peace and Security, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    re financial contributions; and related routine.
  - Coalition of Northeastern Governors, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 4a)
  - Coalition to Protect Social Security, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Coban, Vincentiu-Cristian, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Requesting assistance for his wife to obtain an exit visa from Romania.
  - Coca Cola Company, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Correspondence regarding the production of Coca Cola clothing.
  - Columbia Foundation, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Columbia University [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Invitations to participate in seminars, programs and conferences.
  - Columbia University [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Commendations, 1975-1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Correspondence from members and non-members complimenting the ILGWU and Chaikin.
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 1 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    (Chaikin, member of U.S. delegation) Correspondence and statement re trial of Dr. Yuri Orlov; also materials re Chaikin as member of 1980 U.S. delegation to the Madrid CSCE meetings.
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 2 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 3 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 4 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 5 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 6 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Commission On Security and Cooperation In Europe (U.S. Dept. of State) [folder 7 of 7], 1977- 1980 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Commission on the Holocaust, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    (Chaikin, member) Related routine.
  - Commission on U.S.-Brazilian Relations, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    (Chaikin, member) Includes report of the Commission.
  - Committee for A Democratic Majority, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Committee for the Free World, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Committee For Modern Courts, Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    (Chaikin, member) Correspondence re court reform legislation.
  - Committee For National Health Insurance, 1976-1986 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    (Chaikin, member, Board of Directors) Related routine.
  - Committee For the N.Y.S. Festival, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    (Chaikin, Vice-Chairman) Related routine.
  - Committee of Concerned Scientists, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Committee On Developing American Capitalism, 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    (Chaikin, member) Includes newsletter, minutes, policy statement and correspondence.
  - Committee On the Present Danger [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    (Chaikin, member) Releases, pamphlets, reports and correspondence.
  - Committee On the Present Danger [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Taxation (N.Y.C. Task Force), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    Correspondence and 14 p. proposed recommendations.
  - Complaints, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    From anonymous ILG member re non-union shops sending work out of New York City.
  - Computers, 1974-1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Correspondence re computer systems for ILG offices.
  - Conference Board, 1976-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    re health care conference, and foreign competition.
  - Conference Invitations, 1976-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Invitations from various groups to participate in conferences.
  - Congressional Friends of Human Rights Monitors, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1979-1981 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    (Chaikin, member) re fund raising.